( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
If not me, then who?
Surprise!
Dear, please understand your father.
He's just worried about you.
But not in every situation
should you rely on a gun.
But you know, you're right.
He has a new lead on our case.
Choose Senator Quintin!
You can guarantee that we can rely on him!
In service, you won't be left hanging!
A sure win for our nation!
Please sit down. Please sit down.
Senator Quintin
is our asset in the Senate.
Because of him, we're able
to secure a huge budget
to support our operations.
The great success of our agency
is because of him.
Yes! Norberto is right.
Just think of me as your bank.
Because I have an interest in all of you.
Bank, then, interest!
You know? I have a lot of bank jokes.
It made me cry!
So serious that I could marry this matter.
Sorry, sir, I just thought
it was still joke time.
This is a serious matter.
Because this is about Congressman Salazar!
Congressman Salazar is an ally.
- You know that.
- Yes.
My political ally.
Our bond has become so deep already.
We've already attended so many funerals,
weddings, and christenings together.
But…
there are rumors
about party-list representative Salazar.
The truth is, the one
they call "The Good Congressman"
is only pretending
that he is an anti-crime advocate.
But the truth is,
he is the leader of a local syndicate
called the "Sinigang Cartel".
It was called the Sinigang Cartel
because their group
has many ingredients in the mix.
Politicians, businessmen,
and street operators.
So when the Moravianos
arrived in the country,
this group was threatened,
and Congressman Salazar
tried to undermine the Moravianos
by using his power
and influence in Congress.
The result?
The Moravianos silenced Salazar.
Now,
I'm afraid that a war is coming
between two large and violent syndicates.
The Moravianos on the one hand.
The Sinigang Cartel on the other one.
Okay.
Why are there so many weirdos
in this university?
Anyway, Angelito.
Just focus.
Okay.
Why couldn't he just be honest?
Instead of already being
in her gown and all,
then running away from the church,
he could’ve just texted her instead.
"Hey, love.
I think we shouldn't go through
with our wedding
because there's a sniper rifle
aimed at you.
Because of my Italian best friend
who turns out to be obsessed with me."
Right?
But he didn't do that.
That's why Tintin is so mad at him,
because she thought she was left
at the altar for no reason.
She doesn't know that he did that
because he's sacrificing his own happiness
just so she can live.
Sweetheart, I told you, didn't I?
We're watching a great love story.
You can see it yourself.
It really is a super great love story.
It's just not logical,
but it's still great.
True.
That's why you fall in love.
Because you love.
Hello? Who's this?
Hello, ma'am!
Why? What do you need from him?
And I just want to say that Mr. Pinagpala
has qualified for a personal loan
that he can use for travel,
home improvement, medical expenses,
and other personal plans!
Let's just see each other tomorrow.
Huh?
Oh, no!
Why? Okay, I'll take you home.
No need.
I know you're tired, too.
You need to rest.
Chiara…
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm not made of stone.
I know that
you're already frustrated
with our relationship.
You're right, anyway.
I have so much on my mind.
I’ve been doing a lot of things.
And the one I'm sacrificing
is you.
Well, I can't really blame you either.
Because I was the one
who put you in that situation. So…
I guess that's really
how it's supposed to be, right?
We can't dictate fate,
who we get to meet in life.
Like when we first met.
Okay.
What's the deal?
First, do everything you need to do.
So that you won't need
to think about me for now.
But when you’re done,
when you're okay again,
you'll take me all over the world.
We'll travel the whole world,
just the two of us.
Bok!
What are you doing?
Why did you sound like you're doing
a loan shark business?
I told you, call Mikoy
because he needs
to get this new information.
Chiara was the one who answered.
They're together right now.
Maybe they're all lovey-dovey.
I think we need to restore
the surveillance inside Mikoy's condo.
Mikoy doesn't like being watched.
So we need to be careful
when we call or contact him.
So our asset won't be compromised.
Let's go.
Hey.
What happened to the person
who gets mad whenever
his privacy gets violated?
But when it comes to the bullies,
he can’t do anything.
Why do you care about my life?
Ouch!
You know? You're hurting my feelings.
We've been sleeping together
for several nights now.
So, of course, I'm concerned about you.
You can see it now, right?
You can see what I have to deal with.
So, please. Don't add to it anymore.
I already have so much on my mind.
I don't know what to do
if you pile on too.
I'm just being a friend
who's willing to help you
with those bullies.
You know?
Asking others for help is not a weakness.
And no joke. Just say it,
and I'll punch that Owen guy.
What?
There's no need.
Don't get involved anymore.
And don't add yourself to the mess either.
I can handle this.
We thought the Philippines
was just one of their many branches.
Turns out these Moravianos
are even more ambitious.
Do you remember
Congressman Celestino Salazar?
We have a very reliable source
saying that he was killed
because he wasn't
investigating the Moravianos.
Literally, he was their rival syndicate.
And apparently, our good congressman here
is the leader of the rival gang.
Its name is the Sinigang Cartel.
So sour!
It’s really sour!
Especially their operations.
Illegal gambling, trafficking,
prostitution,
gun running, name it.
But what's really even more sour
are our friends here.
Because they want to rule
here in the Philippines.
Who did this?
Newcomers.
Outsiders.
They go by the name of Moraviano.
With interest, too!
But why do they want
to rule here in the Philippines?
Well, in recent years,
there's been a heavy crackdown
on organized crime in Europe.
So life became harder for them in Prague,
or the whole Czech Republic.
They want to move their operations here.
Because here in the Philippines,
life is easier for them.
And aren't we known all over the world?
We are the most hospitable country
in the world.
Unfortunately, we welcome criminals.
And sometimes, we even vote for them.
That's why they say,
"It's more fun in the Philippines."
Especially now that there’s a new base
of operations for the Moravianos.
Not just for you,
but also for Mikoy.
He's been working so hard at Vertex.
So, he deserves to be celebrated too.
Well, I think he'll like that, Papa.
Agent Alex,
I… I have a problem.
I need your help.
Mikoy, all you need to do
is continue working at Vertex.
And I'm sure there are
other people inside the Moravianos
who know about their illegal operations.
Wait, this isn't about Vertex.
If this is about the Sinigang Cartel,
you shouldn't worry about it.
We are monitoring them as well.
And we think they won't retaliate anymore
because they've been crippled
by the Moravianos.
There you go again,
always thinking about work.
This isn't about work.
I just wanted to ask something.
About…
About Chiara.
What is Chiara’s problem?
All my plates are wrong!
I thought you were smart!
I thought you were good!
Why did I only get barely passing grades?
You sabotaged my grades!
I didn’t have enough time.
I also have my own assignments to finish.
Hey.
I don't care about your assignments.
Next time, you focus
on everything I make you do.
Because this is your last chance.
If you mess up again,
you'll go through something
even worse than this.
Okay?!
Leave!
Hurry up!
So slow.
Move faster!
Leave, I said!
‪Wow.
You're really something else.
He’s so frustrating.
Excuse me!
I just want to tell you all
to stop bothering Angelito.
And from now on,
you will do your own coursework.
And none of you are allowed to bully him.
- Understood?!
- She’s nothing.
Who are you? Are you his bodyguard?
Something like that.
- Well then, boys?
- She's brave.
Let’s see if she's got what it takes.
What about you?! You want to fight, huh?!
You know, I feel guilty about her.
Even in this situation,
she’s still special to me.
Just because I’m spying
on her mom and dad,
it doesn’t mean I stopped
caring about her.
Of course, I still want
to protect our relationship.
So, what’s the problem?
I just want to make it up to her.
You know?
Do something… special for her.
Why are you asking me?
Because you’re a girl.
So, what could it be?
What could it be?
What would make her happy?
Any suggestions? Come on.
Give her flowers, chocolates.
Wrong answer!
Flowers and chocolates again?
Is there really nothing else?
There’s no originality.
It’s like it lacks imagination.
Designer bags?
Designer shoes?
Wrong answer again!
Isn’t she rich?
And her parents are part of a syndicate.
Do you think they’ll be impressed
by designer stuff?
No.
Go on a vacation together.
Hold on. Have you ever been in love?
It seems you don't have
any romance in your bones.
After years of being undercover,
do you think I still
have time for hookups?
Woah.
You know, I don’t want to judge,
but I’ll judge you.
Your life sounds kind of sad.
My happiness isn’t about
whether I have a man or not.
My happiness is putting criminals in jail.
You know, they should build you a statue.
You’re something else.
Have you ever thought about it?
That if Chiara discovers the truth,
that you’re spying on her parents,
she’ll get heartbroken?
I don’t want to be the bearer
of bad news, Mikoy,
but once the truth comes out,
it’s possible that your relationship
won’t survive.
Of course, I’ve thought about it.
That’s why I’m thinking
of romantic moments, right?
Something big and different.
So that somehow, when she finds out
I’ve been lying to her…
I hope she remembers
the happy moments we’ve had together.
Even though I’m pretending to be an agent,
well, she knows that,
you know… that I’m true to her.
My heart is real.
Right?
Do you watch K-dramas?
Sweetheart?
- Is there a problem?
- Huh?
No, there’s no problem.
I just finished early today.
That’s why I wanted to see you.
- Wow!
- What?
Mr. Busy Man has time now!
I was about to get mad at you.
Do you want to go out?
Actually, that was my plan.
So? Let’s go? Let’s go out.
What did Mr. Mikoy D. Pinagpala eat today?
Whatever it is,
keep eating it
because I like this version of you.
Didn’t I tell you I’ll make it up to you?
It’s true that I owe you a lot.
I haven’t had time for you.
I might get used to this.
So? Shall we go?
It’s so humanizing that you’re with Mikoy.
I spent the whole day with Mikoy,
and he has a lot of corny pickup lines.
Do you know what it’s called?
Affection.
Love.
Who is that?
Chiara Valtrovi.
We need to involve his daughter.
We need to smoke them out.
So we can wipe out those pests.
We need a party!
A celebration!
No need for a welcoming party.
It’s time for the whole Philippines
to meet the Valtrovi family.